youth4work.com 2011-12-04

# Youth for work ensures privacy of students from college and university and helps in job search and aiding recruitment process of companies

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy hereby incorporates by reference all terms, conditions rules, policies and guidelines on the Site including the Youth4work Terms of Service.

Youth4work.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:

Details 

When you participate on the youth4work.com web site, we request certain information. Youth4work.com does not share any of your personally identifiable or transactional information with any person or entity. No other third party receives your personally identifiable information or other transactional data except for those with whom you have transactions.

Youth4work.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which the Site links or to which link to the Site. By clicking on a link, logo or other item, or using certain services available on the Site, including the online communication services, please note that you may no longer be on the Youth4work.com Site.

From time to time, Youth4work.com may use customer information for new, innovative and unanticipated uses not previously disclosed or described in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to the Youth4work.com web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses or changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.

Communication Policy

We Provide an Online listing for corporate projects to our huge college students & Professors user base. The private and shared areas of the Site facilitate communication and the exchange and sharing of information between Students and Corporate. The information contained in private on the site shared between Students and Corporate is not used for any purposes other than to facilitate communication and the exchange of Information between them.Youth4work.com reserves the right to monitor communications in the Workroom in order to verify compliance with our Terms of Services.
